const NounQuestion = [
  {
      question: "Which of the following is a noun?",
      options: ["Run", " Yesterday ", "Five", "Beautiful"],
      correct_option: "Run"
    },
    {
      question: "Identify the noun in the sentence: The cat sat on the mat.?",
      options: ["Cat", " Sat ", "The", "On"],
      correct_option: "Cat"
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct noun to complete the sentence: I have a ___.?",
      options: ["Tomorrow", " Happy ", "Ball", "Table"],
      correct_option: "Ball"
    },
    {
      question: "In the sentence The dog barks loudly, what is the noun?",
      options: ["The", " Dog ", "Barks", "Loudly"],
      correct_option: "Dog"
    },
    {
      question: "Select the noun from the options:?",
      options: ["Cloud", " Quickly ", "Tall", "Jump"],
      correct_option: "Cloud"
    },
    {
      question: "Identify the noun in the sentence: She reads books.?",
      options: ["She", "Reads  ", "Books", "None of the above"],
      correct_option: "Books"
    },
    {
      question: "Which word in the sentence is NOT a noun: The sun shines brightly.?",
      options: ["The", "Sun  ", "Shines", "None of the above"],
      correct_option: "Shines"
    },
    {
      question: "What type of noun is used in the sentence: The car is red?",
      options: ["Proper noun", " Common noun ", "Abstract noun", "Collective noun"],
      correct_option: "Common noun"
    },
    {
      question: "In the sentence The boy eats an apple. what is the noun?",
      options: ["Boy", " Eats ", "Apple", "An"],
      correct_option: "Apple"
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct noun to complete the sentence: She has a ___.?",
      options: ["Pen", " Happy", "Big", "Quickly"],
      correct_option: "Pen"
    },
];
export default NounQuestion;
